- ♪ In the
not-too-distant future ♪
♪ Next Sunday A.D. ♪
♪ There was a guy named Joel ♪
♪ Not too different
from you or me ♪
♪ He worked at
Gizmonic Institute ♪
♪ Just another face in a
red jumpsuit ♪
♪ He did a good job
cleaning up the place ♪
♪ But his bosses
didn't like him ♪
♪ So they shot him into space ♪
♪ We'll send him cheesy movies ♪
♪ The worst we can find ♪
♪ La-la-la ♪
♪ He'll have to sit and
watch them all ♪
♪ And we'll monitor his mind ♪
♪ La-la-la ♪
♪ Now keep in mind Joel
can't control ♪
♪ Where the movies
begin or end ♪
♪ La-la-la ♪
♪ Because he used those
special parts ♪
♪ To make his robot friends ♪
♪ Robot Roll Call ♪
- All right, let's go!
♪ Cambot ♪
- Pan left!
♪ Gypsy ♪
- Hi, girl!
♪ Tom Servo ♪
- What a cool guy!
♪ Croooow ♪
- He's a wisecracker.
♪ If you're wondering how
he eats and breathes ♪
♪ and other science facts ♪
♪ La la la ♪
♪ Then repeat to yourself,
it's just a show ♪
♪ I should really just relax ♪
♪ For Mystery Science
Theater 3000 ♪
(guitar twangs)
(mechanical whirring)
(doors closing)
- [Magic Voice] 30 seconds
to commercial sign.
- Hi everybody, welcome
to the Satellite of Love.
I'm Joel, I'm still
trapped in outer space
and still trying to maintain
my sunny disposition.
As you can see, I've redecorated
the Satellite of Love,
so if I ever do make it
off this satellite
and get back to Earth, I
can do talk show panels.
- [Magic Voice] Commercial
sign in 15 seconds.
- Crow made this batch
of brownies here
and we're gonna be
enjoying those.
We ran out of milk, though.
I'll have to use Tang.
- Ick.
- To drink with them.
- [Magic Voice] Commercial
sign in five, four, three, two,
commercial sign now.
- Don't go away, we'll
be right back.
If you do have to go away,
just come back in a
couple of minutes.
My guests will be Tom
Servo and the Amazing Crow.
(instrumental theme music)
Oh man, Crow, those were
great brownies
but we haven't had brownie
fixings around here
for a long time.
What were they?
- Uh, uh hey, is that
a new jumpsuit, Joel?
- Oh, we got the scientists
calling, look oppressed.
- Whew.
- Come in Joel, my little
bagel with a shmear.
(chuckling)
- Hey sirs, what's up?
- Our income if this new
gig works out.
- Yes, Larry and I have
developed a new chain
of fast food restaurants
with very low overhead
because we don't cook our food.
- 'Cause frying and broiling
takes out a lot of
the nutrients.
- Yes, if your body
likes another body,
why don't you try one of
our burgers au natural?
It's ripped from the bone
to your plate in seconds.
It's Clay and Lar's Flesh Barn.
(chuckles)
Make with the lyrics, Lar.
♪ If you're tired of the
same old fare ♪
♪ You got a friend in
Clay and Lar ♪
♪ Our meat is guaranteed rare ♪
♪ Because we don't cook it ♪
- You see, cooking takes
out all the flavor.
♪ If you're tired of cookin'
at home ♪
♪ Try our meat right
off the bone ♪
♪ If you listen, you can
hear it moan ♪
♪ Because we don't cook it ♪
- Stunned, killed right
at your table,
eviscerated very fresh.
♪ Now there's no need for
you to drive through ♪
♪ Our fresh meat'll
walk out to you ♪
♪ You'll say hi, he'll say moo ♪
♪ It's Clay and Lar's
Flesh Barn ♪
- 15 locations to serve
you, now in Altoona.
- Oh well, what I
have this week is
I just got kinda bored in
the bathroom and I made this.
As you can see, it's a,
built a roll of toilet
paper in a two-liter bottle.
What do you think, sirs?
- Great.
- Yeah.
- You could use it for a
Molotov cocktail or something.
- Aw, you guys twist everything.
You could have made
tiddlywinks evil!
- [Both] Thank you!
- Well your film this week,
Joel, is a little number
called Women of the
Prehistoric Planet.
There's really no reason for
it, it just is what it is.
Deal with it, muskie-breath.
- Enjoy!
(alarms blaring)
- Oh, we got movie sign!
(yelling)
(mechanical whirring)
(dramatic music)
- [Joel] I still think that
toilet paper was a good idea.
- [Tom] I just don't understand.
- [Joel] Women of the
Prehistoric Planet,
my sister saw this in
junior high.
All the boys had to go
into the gym.
- [Tom] Wendell Corey,
man among men.
- [Joel] John Agar!
- [Tom] We wish you a
Merry Anders.
Kam Tong, Kam Tong races.
- [Joel] You are here.
Uh, what's that, Servo?
- [Tom] I think it's
the creamy nougat center
of the Milky Way galaxy.
There's the caramel
constellation.
- [Crow] It's so beautiful.
Looks like crud on a windshield.
- [Tom] The cosmic sneeze.
- [Crow] That's beautiful.
Hey look, it's a Lady Remington.
- [Joel] Looks like tinfoil.
- [Tom] It's a steam iron.
- [Crow] Ah, it's a
biscuit warmer.
- [Joel] A chrome watermelon.
- [Tom] It's a metal football.
- [Joel] It's one of
Gallagher's hats.
- [Tom] It's any piece
of alternative reality
we choose it to be,
- [Joel] That's no
alternative piece of reality,
that's a battle station!
- Make an entry in the log book.
- [Joel] A big one.
- On this day, we,
Command Ship Cosmos One...
- [Joel] You know, he
must hit his head
on that beam all the time.
- Six months, 18 days...
- [Tom] Probably doesn't
even feel it anymore.
- Cosmos Two and Three
are following
at three-month intervals,
as programmed.
- [Tom] Looks like a
great big Erector set.
- We continue, homeward
bound, without incident.
- [Crow] Talking to ourselves.
- Well Doc, you better dust
off your dress uniform.
- [Joel] The strapless one?
- Commander, you've
been saying that
for the past six months.
- [Tom] That's the
biggest Pop-o-matic bubble
I think I've ever seen.
- [Crow] I think it looks like
a big Joe Namath popcorn popper.
- Positive.
- [Joel] That's the biggest
guitar I've ever seen,
built right into the
wall behind them.
- Might as well be a year.
That's how long it seems
since we left Centaurus.
- [Tom] Thanks for
the exposition.
- One month and 12 days
Commander Scott just mentioned.
Is that our time here in
space, or time at home?
- [Crow] Uh, you're new
here, aren't you, Elvis?
- About six years back home.
- Six more years.
Brother.
- [Joel] Thank you, Colonel.
- You know something, sir?
We've been gone so long,
my kid brother
is now 30 years older than me.
Is that crazy?
- That's what happens when you
travel at near-optic speeds.
- [Tom] It's kooky, Colonel.
- I suppose in some
ways it is crazy.
- Imagine what would happen
if a married guy came
home after five years
and found his wife was
an old woman.
- [Crow] Oh, I don't even
wanna think about that.
- [Joel] That's not funny,
corporal.
- That's why married
men can't qualify
for cosmic expeditions,
sergeant.
(beeping)
Distress signal from
Cosmos Three!
- You have their coordinates,
Mr. Scott.
Try to get an accurate
fix on their position.
- [Tom] I'll work on getting
these chicks hatched.
- - Communications, King.
- [Joel] Communications queen,
come in.
- Yes sir, clearing
all channels.
- [Crow] Yes, your highn-ass.
- I have a fix on Cosmos Three,
admiral.
- [Joel] How do you
bar chord again?
- They're here in the
Solaris star system.
- [Crow] They're over
by E-minor, or C-sharp.
- That could be a dangerous
area to be off-course.
Solaris is a new star,
surrounded by numerous planets
and a great deal of cosmic gas.
- [Tom] Must be from
the cosmic chili.
- Those gas clouds at
full acceleration,
they'll burn up in an instant.
- [Crow] And we'll be
there to watch!
- Communications, anything
from Cosmos Three?
- Nothing yet, admiral.
We have all channels wide open.
- Try to contact them,
I'll be right in.
Sergeant, reduce
speed one-eight.
- [Crow] And try to pretend
that meant something.
- No sense in getting,
we've got between us
(mumbles) possible.
- [Tom] What?
- [Joel] We've got
between our ears.
- Prepare to reduce programmed
acceleration by one-eight.
- [Joel] Think they're
gonna be the comic relief?
I just got a feeling.
- Did you hear what I heard, Mr.
Bradley?
We're reducing speed.
- I heard.
- [Tom] They're
pretty well-groomed
for having been in
space for so long.
- Not with Scott navigating.
He knows where we were,
where we are
and where we're going to
be at any given moment,
past, present or future.
- [Crow] And all from the
horoscope charts
he got from Nancy Reagan.
- I'll check it out, stand by,
chief.
- [Computer] Activate maneuver.
- Don't tell me he's
thinking of turning back.
- [Joel] Uh, he's
- What would you do?
- [Joel] Turn back.
- There's 20 people and a
valuable cargo
of gravitite aboard that ship.
There is responsibility.
- Correction, Doc.
There are 12 men and a cargo
aboard the Cosmos Three.
The rest are Centaurians.
- [Doc] Oh, yes, yes.
- [Joel] All wearing dickies.
- You don't consider Centaurians
people, do you Scott?
- I don't think we should put
so much trust in 'em,
that's all.
- [Crow] Let's lock 'em
all in relocation camps.
- [Joel] Hey, Pink Lady.
- [Admiral King]
These Centaurians
once had a very high culture,
Scott.
- [Tom] And Jeff.
- They could again
with our help.
- You sound exactly
like the admiral.
- [Crow] And you sound
like Archie Bunker.
- Your sense of values
have changed.
- A deep space colony
can't always live by
the standards we do back home.
- Admiral King's theory
of cosmic colonization.
- [Joel] Is that a Ray
Stevens song?
- It's a required reading
at the academy, Dr. Farrell.
- Commander, if you try
getting to know the admiral,
you might discover he's
quite a remarkable man.
- [Joel] And really quite
stunning, when you think about
it.
- I've been with him on
Centaurus
for the past three years.
- [Joel] La dee dah.
- I think I know him
pretty well.
- [Joel] And you're no
Jack Kennedy, Senator!
- I believe I know him better.
- [Crow] Yeah, well my
dad can beat up your dad.
- Cosmos Three, Command
Ship One to Cosmos Three.
- [Joel] Disinflating Annette's
hair, starting on my mark.
- If you are receiving,
please acknowledge.
- Shall we keep trying, sir?
- Cosmos Three, this is
Admiral King.
If you are receiving,
please advise Captain Ross
that he's off-course and
approaching a dangerous area.
Repeat, your present course
will take you into a
danger zone.
- [Joel] Watts.
- Keep trying.
Repeat the same message,
on all channels.
- [Crow] In your voice, sir?
- Admiral King, do you think
something has happened to them?
- We don't know yet, Linda.
- I have friends aboard
the Cosmos Three.
I am afraid for them.
- We all have friends
on Cosmos Three.
We're all deeply concerned.
- [Joel] So concerned that I
felt compelled to touch you.
- Cosmos Fleet Command
Ship One to Cosmos Three.
- [Tom] Pigs in space!
- [Cosmos One] Cosmos One
to Cosmos Three.
- [Joel] They're dead.
- [Cosmos One] If you can
transmit, please acknowledge.
- Tang, you've got to
listen to me. Both of you.
Put away those guns,
it'll soon be too late!
- No.
- [Crow] No way, old man.
- Can't you understand,
this ship is out of control!
Unless you release those
men in the maneuvering room,
we're going nowhere but
to our deaths!
- They're trying to trick us.
- I am not trying to--
(punch landing)
- You, Lieutenant Anderson.
You will take us back
to Centaurus.
- You stupid fools!
- [Joel] It's
pronounced Megtaurus.
- He said the Centaurians
couldn't be trusted.
- Tang, what are you doing?
- [Joel] Think of us as
Klingons without the cling.
- We're getting back
to Centaurus.
- Tang, this is treasonous, do--
- Very strong magnetic field,
sir.
We're locked in.
- It's one of the
planets of Solaris.
We've entered its
field of gravity.
- Activate the decelerator,
sergeant.
- What does it mean, captain?
- It's no use.
It means that we're doomed
to crash into that planet
unless I can regain control
of the maneuvering room.
- [All] Not again!
- [Tom] And that playground
ball's a threat too.
- Then we shall crash.
It is better that we
die than be your slaves.
- We have never treated
you as a slave.
- [Crow] Yeah, what about
that one time?
- The captain knows
what it's about--
(punches landing)
- [Tom] We're gonna crash
into a Universal picture!
(instrumental theme music)
(whirring)
- [Joel] Fakey.
- [All] Fakey.
Real.
- [Joel] Dead guy.
- [All] Fakey.
Real.
- [Tom] Real fakey.
- [Joel] Fake guys.
Filmed on location in
Tommy Ronick's front yard.
(splashing)
(dramatic music)
- [Tom] They're hammered.
- [Joel] And the
chicks are dead.
- What do you suppose
happened to them, admiral?
- [Crow] Ah, they probably
crashed in Tommy's front yard.
- Cosmic clouds.
- [Joel] Yellow moons, pink
hearts, all that stuff.
- It shouldn't.
- I wonder how they got so
far off-course.
I mean, it's impossible
they didn't know.
- No question about it, admiral.
They're grounded on one of
the inner planets of Solaris.
- [Joel] Yikes.
- Communications,
anything coming in?
- No, admiral, nothing
but the homing signal.
- Any reply from
command headquarters?
- Nothing yet, admiral.
- Keep me informed.
- [Crow] Well, that's not
gonna be easy.
You're kind of a muttonhead.
(beeping)
- The admiral is really upset,
isn't he?
- [Joel] Hmm, yeah.
- It's the first ship
he's ever lost.
- [Tom] Lost his keys a few
times, but never the whole ship.
- Do you think he
will turn back?
- [Joel] Probably.
- If command'll let him,
he will.
- I don't think so,
we're too close to home.
- You know we'll
never get there.
It is just a wishful dream.
- I know what you mean, honey.
- [Crow] Uh-oh.
Moron patrol.
- This isn't exactly what
I call a pleasure party.
- Well it could be, sugar,
if you'd let yourself go.
- Well, well, the wolf
of outer space.
And who let you out of
your darkened den?
- Now be kind to me, ladies.
Don't forget that I'm
your ingenious engineer,
the master of the
maneuvering room
and the activator of
your gravity.
- [Tom] Not to mention
a flatulating butthead.
- Here we go again.
Well I suppose we are grateful
for all these amazing
services, Mr. Bradley.
- Lieutenant, you just
allow this sweet thing
a few moments' liberty
with your little star mate
and well, I'll consider
you all paid in full.
- [Joel] He's done everything
but insult the Centaurian.
- Now Lieutenant,
there's no reason
for you to treat me like
a common old Centaurian.
- [All] Oops.
- Hey Linda, I'm sorry.
You know I didn't mean
anything by what I said.
You know me, I could
light up a whole room.
(laughing)
Just by walking out.
- [All] Yay.
(clapping)
- Forget it, Linda, he
didn't mean it.
- You know, she's right.
I mean, Lieutenant
Bradley's crazy about you.
- [Crow] Hey, check out
those space-age lockers.
- You know that.
- Yes, I know.
But I wonder if your people
really can accept us, Karen.
- Listen Linda, you
have an exciting
new life ahead of you.
Don't worry about
being accepted.
- [Tom] 'Cause you won't be.
- When you get around to
all those young cadets
at the academy, you'll
forget all about Centaurus,
those years in the colonies
and people with narrow minds.
- [Crow] Among other things.
- You know, I've
barely ever seen
a boy of my own age.
- [Joel] I'm
resetting the controls
so they crash into the
prehistoric planet.
- Command headquarters!
(beeping)
- [Crow] Do I look good up here?
- The reply from Space Command,
Mr. Scott.
- [Joel] It says, "Do not
tear, spindle or mutilate!"
- Communique from headquarters,
admiral.
- [Joel] Looks like your agent's
not gonna get you
outta this one.
- No other communications
can be established,
it must be assumed that
Cosmos Three has crashed,
killing all crew members
and passengers.
- [Joel] He's right.
- We regret your request to
return to star system Solaris
to search for survivors
must be denied.
Continue on course
as programmed.
- [Joel] Signed,
Zippy the chimp.
- [Tom] Huh?
- It would have been a
futile effort, admiral.
- We will reverse our course,
Mr. Scott.
Program a flight plan
to take us to Solaris.
- But sir, the request has been
denied by Command headquarters.
- I'm the commander
of this fleet.
All the passengers and
crewmen on these ships
are my responsibility as
long as we are in deep space.
We are still in space.
- [Crow] Well, they're in
deep something.
- Is that clear, Mr. Scott?
- [Joel] Hold me.
- Yes, sir.
- Send a communique to
Command headquarters
to that effect immediately.
- Evans, stand by to
reverse course.
Horizontal maneuver.
- Yes, sir.
- [Joel] That's how he
got that job.
- Maneuvering room,
this is Control.
Stand by horixontal activators,
we're changing course.
- [Crow] And beam up more Dep.
- Maneuvering room standing by.
- I'll talk to you later, sugar.
- [Joel] I just made out on
the phone, this is great!
- What is all this, Mr. Bradley?
First we slow down to a walk.
- [Joel] It's a control
panel, you should know that.
- Looks like we're going back,
chief.
- You mean Space Command
okayed the old man's request?
- Well if they didn't,
he's sure gonna catch
it when we do get home.
- Maneuvering room from Control.
New course is one-seven-five
degrees on horizontal plane.
- One-seven-five horizontal.
(switches clicking)
- Programmed.
- [Tom] That's all
you have to do?
- Set automatic pilot on
Cosmos Three's homing beam
for three months' cruising,
full acceleration.
- Three months?
Yes, sir.
- [Joel] I got this Snoopy
ruler for free.
What do you think, Tom?
Anybody?
- [Tom] People always seem
to comfort her.
(dramatic music)
- [Crow] Even our name
says Merry Christmas.
- [Crow] Gilligan!
- [Tom] Skipper!
- [Crow] Mary Anne!
- [Tom] Ginger!
Thurston?
- [Crow] Lovey?
- [Tom] Wrong-way?
- [Crow] Japanese guy!
Hey, the mummy's getting better.
- We'll stop here for the night.
At least it's dry ground.
- [Crow] Yeah, rest here,
maybe we can find your scalp.
Hey, here's some mossy lichen.
We could make a wig out
of it for ya.
- Don't touch me!
I told you to stay away from me.
- I only want to help you,
lieutenant.
You need help.
- [Joel] Yeah, but you
put my arm in a sling
and it doesn't even hurt.
- None of us would
need any help.
- I'm sorry for what has
happened, but I didn't rebel.
- Jang was your brother,
what's the difference?
- Jang thinks for himself.
I am not responsible.
- You're all alike.
You take everything from
us and you give nothing.
I hate all of you.
- But Sally, we were friends
only a few hours ago,
- [Tom] I'm Johnny Longtorso.
Can I be of any help here?
- Leave me alone, please!
- [Crow] Maybe this
isn't a good time,
but could you launder my pants?
- No, Zenda, I don't
hate you but...
- But you wish you'd
never heard of Centaurus.
- I didn't say that.
- [Joel] Let's just say
that I don't hate you.
I'm not gonna call you
for racquetball,
if that's what you mean.
I wonder what she wanted.
- [Tom] Here's my card,
Johnny Longtorso.
- Here, Sally.
- [Joel] It's Pez.
Make you feel better.
- It'll kill the pain.
- [Crow] And here, it's
my Motorman's Helper.
- [Joel] Finish it!
- I wish I could do more.
I wish I were a doctor.
- [Joel] I wish I were a
pixie, but let's get real.
- You wished for her
and you got her.
What did I get, nothing.
Well I'm gonna try wishing.
I wish I was dead!
- [Tom] That can be arranged.
- We're gonna be all right.
Admiral King'll come
back for us.
Cosmos One's probably on its
way here this very minute.
- [Tom] And hey, you got
a sling outta the deal
and it's a pretty neat one.
- Even if they know
where we are.
Command headquarters will
never let him turn back.
- [Joel] We're too
annoying for anyone
to consider picking us up,
it's over.
- I know Admiral King too,
Anyway, we've got to hope,
Sally.
- [Crow] Nice speech,
now can I get some sleep,
for goodness sake?
- [Joel] Nice statue.
Oh, she's real.
- [Tom] Weren't you in
Bali H'ai, or Hawaiian Eye?
- You'd better get some rest,
Zenda.
We may have a long way to go
before we get out of
this jungle.
- Do you really believe
they'll be back to look for us?
- Of course I do.
- You're a good man, Charles.
- [Crow] Brown.
- Your faith and courage,
even in defeat.
- [Tom] And my feet look
like hell right now.
- We're still alive.
Tomorrow we should be able
to reach the foothills.
It's safer there.
- [Joel] If I read my
script correctly, that is.
- We can still live
on this planet,
if we just trust each other.
- [Tom] We can play
boobly-oobly for years,
and the banana will stick.
- [Joel] Oh, we better
get out of here.
- [Crow] Wonder what she wanted.
(mechanical whirring)
(doors closing)
- Joel, this is your life!
(applauding)
you were an ambitious young man
and began your life in space
as a custodian for
Gizmonic Institute.
Do you remember this voice?
- [Crow] There's an
unidentified satellite
straying into our orbital path!
- Oh, well that's easy,
it's my old friend Crow.
I think he's talking
about the time we partied
with the fellas from
Salyut Seven.
(grunting)
- Joel, Joel, help!
Big satellite, big, death,
danger, wreckage, ouch!
Thing, pain.
Hey, where did this
couch come from anyway?
- I found it in one of the
crates down in the loading bay.
I thought I'd redecorate.
What's this about a
death satellite?
- Oh yeah.
A big, big death satellite.
Oh, big.
Pain, look, run.
Help, help.
- Just settle down,
come up here.
Come on up here and sit down.
Tell me all about it, okay,
just take a few deep breaths.
That's all right.
(breathing deeply)
- Well, there's a big
satellite out there
and we're gonna collide with it.
- What!?
- Ow!
(clattering)
- Cambot, give me an
exterior of the ship, quick!
Jeepers!
- [Crow] What's goin' on?
- Get behind the couch, you two.
The redcoats are coming.
All right, little
death satellite.
Joely's got the exo-pincers on
and he's nobody's sweetheart.
You and me, going round
and round, mano y mano.
Here comes lunch.
Gimme the exo.
That's right, little
doomsday machine.
Come to papa, feel my steel.
Hah hah hah.
Now to bring it inside.
Cambot, gimme the interior shot.
- Do you have to bring
everything you find in space
into the living room?
- Sure looks like a
doomsday device, all right.
Joel, are we up a creek here?
- It's a doomsday machine,
all right, and I think
I accidentally activated
its self-destruct mechanism.
I'd say we have roughly an
hour to disarm this thing.
- [Satellite] Correction, you
have an hour and 37 minutes
to disarm and yes, you
are up a creek.
- Oh, golly.
And we got commercial
sign on top of everything!
(instrumental theme music)
We gotta disarm that satellite,
you two,
or this is serious.
- [Tom] Going down
for the count.
- [Crow] That was no
boating accident!
- [Tom] I'm sorry I had to
kill you, Dave,
but you understand, I
couldn't let you live.
You see, you knew too much.
- [Joel] It's the Green Hornet.
- [Crow] Kato?
(Joel whistling)
- [Crow] You'd think
in the future
they'd be able to
get hip waders.
- [Tom] Oh, very sneaky.
- [Joel] Hey, he's trying to
sneak across the rice paper.
- [Crow] If only I could
get to my utility belt.
(Crow growls)
- [Tom] Smooth.
- [Crow] I'll take that, Mr.
Bond.
- What are you trying to do?
- Someone's out there.
- [Joel] Who could
be out there--
Huh?
- [Tom] Take that, Mr. Moto!
Nerts to you, Confucius.
- [Joel] Bring the car around...
Kato.
- You will not take us back!
- [Crow] Strange way for lodge
brothers to greet each other.
- [Tom] Don't just do
something, stand there!
- [Crow] Tiny bubbles
in my larynx!
(Tom imitates choking)
- [Joel] I'm not on either side,
oop.
- [Tom] Kill your
brother, it's the only way
to reinforce the director's
white male reality.
Take the shot, come on!
(gun firing)
- [Joel] Mom always did
like you best.
- [Crow] Gee, I...
I missed.
- [Joel] I know you
just shot your brother,
but why don't you just
come over here
and love me a little bit?
Yeah.
Hey, help me.
- [Tom] Meanwhile, at
the ocarina.
- 10,000 miles, sir.
- Plot speed miles, five
miles per second.
Alright, Alan, check
gravitation compensators
for an altitude of 50 miles.
Decelerate to zero velocity.
- DC 50 miles, zero velocity.
500.
- [Joel] 500 what?
- 300.
- [Joel] What?
- 200.
- [Joel] Stop teasing me.
- [Alan] 150.
100.
- [Crow] Sold.
- 75.
60, 55.
50.
- [Crow] And so on and so on.
- Stationary orbit, sir.
- 50 miles and locked in, sir.
- Very good, Mr. Scott.
- [Tom] Told you he'd like it.
- [Joel] Hey, Picture Picture.
- Could you join me on the
observation deck, please?
- [Crow] He asked me,
he asked me!
- [Joel] Just let me
slip my dance belt on.
- We've finally arrived.
- Did you have any doubts,
doctor?
- About reaching Solaris?
No.
- [Tom] Let's see, looks
like a hairline fracture.
- What about finding any of
them still alive, Dr. Farrell?
- Well, there's always a chance.
- Not a very good chance,
I believe.
- [Crow] Oh what do you know?
- Yes, the facts do
indicate that this planet
has an unpleasant environment,
but not necessarily hostile.
It has a carbon water
oxygen system.
- [Joel] Sounds kinda
like a Slurpee.
(speaking foreign language)
- [Crow] Hmm?
- Jung has calculated
that for the past
three months while we've
been traveling,
18 years have gone by
on the planet.
- [Tom] That means it'll be
legal to date my girlfriend now.
- [Joel] My CDs should be
rolling over just about now.
- I believe our admiral
will not give up
until he has definite proof
there are no survivors.
- [Crow] He's gonna get
sleeves someday.
- It'll probably cost
him his command.
- Once there were such
leaders on Centaurus.
- If the admiral has his
way, there will be again.
He's determined to prove that
Centaurus can rebuild
its culture.
- [Joel] What a kiss-up.
- Well, I'd say that Linda is
a brilliant example of
what can be done.
- [Crow] Through bizarre
experimentation.
- When she was removed to the
colony, the others were not.
- What are you trying to
tell me, Jung?
- [Tom] I abhor you,
round-eye, and all your ways.
- A people will
change their ways
only if they wish to do so.
A man may be removed
from the land.
- [Crow] Wait, wait, let
me get a pencil here.
- But it is difficult to
remove the land from the man.
- [All] And you can't remove
the land from the man,
the chalice from the palace
has the brew that is true.
- [Tom] The flagon
with the dragon
has the pellet with the poison.
- It's such a beautiful planet.
- [Joel] Hey, settle down,
it's just a painting.
- So clean and peaceful.
- It won't be so
peaceful down there.
- [Tom] Yeah, the grass
is always greener
on the other side of the galaxy.
- [King] You can't trust
young planets.
- What do you mean, admiral?
- [Joel] They're lazy and
they listen to loud music.
- Including things
completely unnoticed.
- Hasn't this planet ever
been explored?
- [King] Not according
to our galactic records.
- [Crow] But then I
couldn't read 'em
'cause I spilled coffee on 'em.
- No sign of life of any kind,
admiral.
Human or otherwise.
- Creatures on these
planets are deceiving.
Even on the ground, you can't
always trust what you see.
- [Joel] Bill, how do you
fight your panty line?
- [Crow] Huh?
Oh, that's man talk.
We'll never understand it.
- 18 years is a long time.
And they couldn't have picked
a worse place to crash.
- [Crow] He says that like
there's a good place to crash.
- Certainly a
botanist's paradise.
- [Joel] I hate to tell
you this, Phil,
but all your aquarium
fish are dead.
- About five million years ago.
Doctor, could man exist
in that environment?
- Probably.
- [Tom] Let's all speak
in broken sentences.
- I think it would be mostly
combating the elements,
defending himself from
who-knows-what.
There could be some
rather ferocious beasts
roaming about that terrain.
- [Crow] Are the scenes
just as static
down on the planet, Bill?
- Inform them we are going to
make a landing on this planet.
- [Tom] Use the good stationery.
- [Joel] Yep.
- That big canyon.
- [Joel] Uh-huh.
- Beyond the jungle.
- [Joel] Yeah, I see it.
- That's your landing site.
- [Tom] Oh.
- Sergeant Alan.
- [Joel] Yep?
Gotcha.
Who should I tell
these orders to?
- Attention all personnel.
Landing stations.
Stand by gravitators.
- Maneuvering room, stand
by gravitators.
- Manuevering room ready
and standing by.
- [Tom] Thanks, Angel.
- I hate to say it,
lieutenant, but I got a feeling
the old man's got a bad
case of cosmic fever.
- [Crow] Well I've got some
salve in my footlocker.
- Where's your spirit of
adventure, chief?
I thought you loved this life.
- Spirit I've got,
adventure I've had.
Love, I was looking forward to.
- I know what you mean, chief.
Look at the words of that
great planeteering prophet.
- Yeah, what'd he say?
- He said, "Let them that
don't want none
"have memories of..."
Forget it.
(laughing)
- [Joel] Great prophet, hope
you didn't get any of that
tattooed anyplace important.
- [Tom] Hey, I see a spot,
let's pull up over there.
(eerie humming)
(instrumental theme music)
- All right, let's take a break.
Go easy on the water.
- [Joel] It
eliminates rest stops.
- Everyone take one
oxygenian tablet.
No more.
- [Crow] I didn't
say Simon Says.
- Like breathing underwater,
hot water.
- You'll get used to it.
- [Tom] It's like being
in the crew's quarters.
- Imagine having to live
in an inferno like this.
- It's probably not too
bad up in the highlands.
- This planet's not too
unlike Centaurus.
- [Joel] Apart from the fact
that it's completely different.
- I imagine the
Centaurians could adapt
to this planet very easily.
- With all this vegetation?
No, they like the deserts, doc.
You give them barren,
windswept oceans of sand--
- [All] Shut up!
- Say, doc.
- [Crow] Do you think I'll
be offed first?
- I mean, Mr. Farrell.
Old Jung says that in the
three months it took us
to get back to this planet,
18 years passed by here.
How does he figure that?
- [Joel] He was kidding!
- I told you half a dozen
times, it's the time paradox.
What's the matter with you?
- [Joel] Oh yeah, I
missed that day.
- I still don't see it.
- It's a matter of
reference points.
- [Crow] Ah, it's too
complicated for you, bonehead.
- On our ship we were
traveling at one speed.
This planet travels at another.
- You get it, kid?
For three months, we've
been barreling along
at near the speed of light.
- Yeah, yeah, I know that.
But I--
- Look, look.
This planet rotates on its axis
at only 1,000 miles an hour.
Now that speed
determines the length
of the day, the month and
the year here.
- We gettin' through?
- [Tom] Why don't you
come up to my room tonight
and I'll explain it to you?
- Look, at the speed we
were traveling in space
for three months, that was
the equivalent of 6,500--
- [Joel] La la la la la,
can't hear you.
La la la la la la la.
- Yeah, sure.
That's simple.
It's just a matter of
reference points.
Anybody can see that.
- [Crow] He's bluffing.
- [Tom] He's a twit.
- See anything?
- A few birds.
Nothing else.
What do you expect to see,
a welcoming committee?
- Don't get funny.
- [Tom] Don't worry, he won't.
- You hear something, chief?
- [Joel] I don't think it's
the welcoming committee.
- Something walking
around up there.
- [Crow] Something big.
- Don't anybody move.
- [Tom] Oh my god, it's an
insert shot of an iguana!
- [Joel] Their technology must
be light years ahead of ours!
Their use of stock
footage is amazing!
Oh great, that's your
answer to everything.
- [Crow] How do you like
your lizard done, boys?
- [Tom] I never knew lizards
were so darn flammable.
- [Joel] No thunder
lizards were hurt
during the filming of this film.
- [Crow] Mmm, extra crispy.
- Dried out?
- [Tom] Sure, can I
go change now?
- Yeah, I think so.
- [Tom] I soiled myself.
- What is it, Alan?
- I can't find a heartbeat.
- Nothing like a little
adventure, eh lieutenant?
- [Joel] Try lower.
- Set up a beamer here.
- [Joel] BMW?
- Cosmos One, this is Scott.
Do you receive me?
- [Crow] Gutless One,
we read you.
- We're receiving you,
commander.
Stevens standing by.
- Ensign, inform the
admiral that I advise
no one be allowed to
leave the ship
without being well-armed.
- Scott, this is King.
- [Tom] Are you speaking
into a Water Pik?
- We've encountered one of those
deceptive creatures you
mentioned, a giant lizard.
It's been destroyed but I'm sure
there are others in this area.
We're about halfway to the
crash site now, admiral.
I'll leave a beamer at
this location.
That's all, sir.
- Very well, Mr. Scott.
Carry on and keep a sharp watch.
Don't want to be caught
with your guard down.
- Yes, sir.
- Very well, Mr. Scott,
carry on.
Keep a sharp watch.
You don't want to be caught
with your guard down.
- [Joel] Stop doing
your Cagney impression,
it's not that great.
- My commanding officer
asked for volunteers
for an important expedition.
I thought he meant exhibition.
- [Crow] Yeah, and my uncle's
the producer on the film, too.
- All right men, let's move.
And keep a sharp watch.
- [Joel] It's our first
Christmas on the planet
and you've been just grand.
We'd better go be with
the others now.
- If that's where they
grow lizards around here,
I'd hate to run into a snake.
- [Joel] Good one.
- [Tom] There's a
well on the ship.
(admiral mumbling)
- [Joel] What?
- Sorry men, your
liberty's canceled.
No one is to leave the ship
under any circumstances.
- Have the located the
Cosmos Three, sir?
- Not yet.
- Well there goes the ball game,
huh?
- They must have run
into trouble out there.
- I wish I was with 'em.
- Anything would be
better than being stuck in
this king-sized
community capsule.
- [Crow] Oh, you.
- Admiral King!
Linda is out of the ship.
- Are you sure?
- She said she wished to
breathe the fresh air,
and feel the warm of the sun.
- [Tom] Just tell me where
she went, Hemingway, come on.
- She's been dying to
get off this ship
ever since we landed.
- [Crow] Will it help if I
strike a pose right here?
- Harris, get my field gear.
- [Joel] And my spare pants.
- Admiral King, you can't
take this chance, sir.
If anything should happen
to you or Commander Scott,
this ship would never
leave this planet.
- [Tom] Yes, you'd be in
charge, yes, I realize that.
- Harris, you and Wilson
go look for her.
- She's probably near the ship.
- Yes, sir.
- Bring laser rifles with you.
- [Crow] I'll stay here
and take more lithium.
- Yes, sir.
- Don't worry, admiral.
We'll find her.
- [Tom] Spin and Marty
to the rescue!
- Poor Linda.
She's such a lost child.
- Karen, if anything
happens to her,
I'll never forgive myself.
- I understand.
- She's just like her mother.
- [Tom] Oh Ward, the
Beaver turned out okay.
- Filled with childlike
dreams of another world.
- [Joel] What is he, Anne of
Green Gables all of a sudden?
Hey!
- Cannot be changed.
(beeping)
- [Crow] What did he want?
- I didn't know he knew
Linda's mother.
I thought she was killed in
the Centaurian tribal war.
- It is true, but the admiral
knew her long before that.
He made many expeditions into
the desert in those years.
- [Crow] Oh wait a minute,
wait a minute.
You're describing the
plot of Kung-Fu.
- Who was Linda's father?
- [Tom] We better get
out of here.
- [Crow] Oh boy.
- [Joel] We gotta disarm
that satellite!
- [Crow] Oh yeah, I wanna help.
- [Joel] Let's get going.
(instrumental theme music)
You know, this makes no
sense at all.
Whoever heard of a
doomsday machine
with a fold-lock top in it?
- Hey, hey Joel, look,
I found a instruction
manual right there, see?
- Thanks.
It says Isaac Asimov
Literary Doomsday Machine.
It's an instruction manual,
must be over 1,000 pages long.
How typical.
- Literary doomsday?
Isn't that when your
library fines
exceed the price of the book?
- I thought it was every
time Jackie Collins
makes it to the
best-seller list.
- Oh, settle down,
you goonheads.
We got this doomsday
machine to disarm,
and well, we gotta
check the manual.
Let's see.
It looks like it's translated
from the Korean or something.
- They must have sub-contracted
the satellite for him.
- I don't get it, Asimov
must have gone mad.
Why would anyone want to
make a doomsday machine?
- Well he's probably
mad because no one else
is as smart as him, or
else that L. Ron Hubbard
has more followers than him.
- Well, didn't Asimov
try to establish
the Church of the
Super Quiz once?
- Oh knock it off, you
spinach-chins.
I gotta read this manual.
Step one, it will be very
enjoyable for you to separate
the ocular filter coupling
of from the decapacitor
which is stout and yellow,
sometimes.
Crow you'd better scan this
and give me the instructions.
(high-pitched whirring)
- Got it!
Okay, most very kindly,
find the looky switch
which is nice and sitting there
with green label that
leaves you singing.
- I think I got it.
- Okay, carefully
disregard and do not do
the very wrong thing or
much confusion will result.
Tell me about it.
With sparks, flowers and
loud report on some models.
Glue Batman to seat G,
detail omitted for clarity?
- This is really confusing.
- Who wrote this,
Charlie Callas?
- Hey, oh, oh, wait,
there's more.
It says clip red wire,
likes you best
with firm hand and glad heart.
- Okay.
I think that oughta do it.
- But first, clip the blue wire.
(evil mechanical laughing)
That's what it said.
(alarms blaring)
- Oh man, we got movie sign.
(all yelling)
(mechanical whirring)
- [Joel] (groaning) My eyes.
- [Tom] You got creamed.
You okay?
- [Joel] Say!
(screaming)
Seems like a nice little booger,
aah!
- [Crow] Are you chafing
like a bear or is it just me?
- I don't know, it sounded
like a bird call to me.
- [Crow] Sounded like a
girl screaming at a snake.
- [Joel] Hey, the snake
pushed her into the river.
- [Tom] Fortunately I have
my Johnny Rocket crossbow.
- [Crow] Snake on a stake.
- [Tom] Hey, look what
someone threw back.
Cool, this'll look great
over the mantel.
I can't believe, this
is a keeper.
- [Crow] Hey, watch those hands.
- [Tom] Amazing what you
find if you just look.
- [Joel] She'll be perfect
for my experiments.
- [Crow] And Quincy
will be so proud of me.
- [Joel] Say, this hotel's
got everything.
I wonder where the game room is.
- Get a load of this place,
will ya?
You're looking at
Paradise Island.
- [Joel] I hear ya, pal.
- Also the end of the trail,
unless you're a mountain goat.
- [Joel] Well, I used to be.
- I think we missed her.
- Maybe she's back
there someplace.
- Tracks.
She's been right around
here someplace.
- [Crow] Like right where
these tracks were made?
- Do you think she fell in?
I mean, do Centaurians
know how to swim?
- I don't know.
Her boot!
- [Crow] Dibs, dibs!
Let me drink champagne out
of it, just to be sure.
- Look at the size
of that thing.
- [Joel] Oh, I've seen
trees bigger than that.
That's nothing.
- Let's get back to the ship.
Let's go, come on, come on,
come on.
- [Tom] We've been pacing
this studio for hours.
When do we get some
action happening?
- [Crow] Hmm, coconut cream
pie, car made out of bamboo,
and a sailor's hat.
What's it all mean?
- All right, let's take five.
- [Tom] One, two, three, four,
five.
(laughing) Psych!
- What's the matter, Bradley?
This hike too much for you?
- Oh no doc, I always
enjoy a 40-mile walk
on a lovely day like this.
- [Crow] You ever see the
movie Alive, donut boy?
- You were 10 pounds overweight.
- Are you kiddin', doc?
I've been on a diet
for seven days,
and so far all I lost is a week.
- [Joel] Good one.
- [Tom] And your
self-respect, for that joke.
- That's the story of my life.
I'm always volunteering
for something.
I remember one time back
at headquarters,
I volunteered for a
karate course.
They taught me all the hits,
the chops,
the head, the neck, the
shoulders, the stomach.
The karate kicks, hah!
- [Crow] Who are you,
Donald O'Connor?
- Hi-keeba, hah!
- [Tom] You know, I
could watch that all day.
Do that again, will ya?
- And after
completing the course,
I became a karate expert.
- [Joel] When did he
become an idiot?
- I went around breaking
boards with my bare hands.
The first time I
saluted Admiral King,
I almost knocked my brains out.
- [Crow] Sure you
didn't succeed?
- For this, this
mission to Centaurus
and look where it got me.
- Like you always told me,
lieutenant,
where's your spirit
of adventure?
- [Tom] I left it in
my other pants.
- That's what makes all of
this worthwhile, the adventure.
Day after day, week after
week, month after month.
Year after year, oh the
sheer thrill of it all.
Perusing the planets,
unifying the universe.
Galloping through the galactics.
- [All] Shut up!
- We'd landed our ship
in the middle of
the densest part of the jungle.
We were about 200 yards
from the ship--
- [Crow] Morty Gunty,
appearing this week at
the Blaine Community Theater
in Shakespeare's King Lear.
- With fire and flame shooting
out of all three nostrils.
Well, I raised my laser gun.
- [Crow] Shut him up.
- But the gun wouldn't work.
It looked like certain
death for all of us.
- [Joel] I can't reach his nose.
- I reached back and I
grabbed a handful of yours,
and I threw it right in the
beast's face and killed it.
- Now, just a minute Red.
You reached back and
grabbed a handful of what?
- Yours, a handful of yours.
And I threw it right in his--
- Okay, okay, Bradley, tell me.
What's yours?
- I'll have a three-day pass,
sir.
(groaning)
- [Tom] Ba-ba-boom!
(goofy laughing)
- Let's move out, shall we?
- [Crow] He'll be
riding in the trunk
on the way back to Earth.
- [Joel] He's a real
child of hell.
(dramatic music)
I gotta get a new log
out here or somethin'.
(animal squeaking)
- [Crow] Ah Wilma, you're up.
- [Joel] Have you met Steve,
my monkey?
- [Tom] You got some
flaking there.
Maybe you could use a henna.
- Pretty girl.
- Who are you?
- I am Tang.
- [Tom] I'm not just
for breakfast anymore.
- [Joel] That's my
favorite drink!
- [Crow] It's short for
Australopithecus Africanus.
- I am Centaurian.
- [Joel] Tang is my
favorite drink.
- You are Centaurian.
We are safe.
- Well how did you get
here, on this planet?
- This is my homeland.
- You were born here.
Your mother was aboard
the Cosmos Three.
- [Tom] Hey, your mother
swims after troop ships, lady.
- Survivors?
- Yes, your mother and father.
Where are they?
- [Joel] Um, you're
wearing them.
- I will take you to them.
- Tang?
- [Crow] Uh, fresh out,
but I got catawba juice.
- Clothes wet, you
fall in water.
- Oh yes, I remember.
- There was a serpent.
- I killed it, I bring you here.
- [Joel] This hot stick.
- [Tom] You'll like 'em.
Leave the shower curtain here.
- [Crow] Oh, by the way,
I did that totem pole
just 'cause I thought I
was supposed to.
- [Tom] How much per
month for this?
With the damage deposit?
(Linda speaking quietly)
- [Crow] Now, join me
in my dance of death.
- [Tom] That's cold.
- It's beautiful.
- Mother.
- [Joel] She's not bad,
except for a little
freezer burn right
around the edges.
- [Tom] It's Clarence Birdseye.
- Lieutenant Anderson!
He's not a Centaurian.
- My father.
- [Crow] Well, they're
no bowling trophies.
- I must tell the
admiral about this.
I must go back to the
ship that brought me here.
Do you know where the ship is,
Tang?
- I know, I take you there.
- [Crow] And then I'll
get some pronouns.
Meanwhile, back at the
dry ice pool.
(pool bubbling)
- [Tom] Oh, that's just mean.
- Yeah, they could use a
spare deodorant.
You rub it on, the smell
stays but you disappear.
- [Joel] Good one.
- It's boiling crude oil,
commander.
- Boy, what a spot for
a steam bath.
- [Joel] Just cross the
log and you're in the club.
- Hand me that rope.
- [Tom] You could walk around.
- [Crow] Too easy.
Sure glad the prop boys laid
this log out here for us.
- [Tom] If the Wallendas
can do it, we can do it.
- He's got more nerve
than I thought he had.
- Scott's a good man, Bradley.
- [Joel] He has wonderful
bone structure,
great teeth and a
darling figure.
- Yeah, but what a miserable
place to have to search.
- [Tom] He's right over there.
- A hazardous mission is
like a mirror of truth.
When you face it, you see
your true self.
- [Crow] Oh shut up,
what are you, Confucius?
Just cross the dry
ice and shut up!
- Why don't you build a
better bridge?
- (chuckling) Wrong
kind of engineers.
- [Joel] Uh, you see, we
just play with toy trains.
- Frankly, yeah.
- Doc, I don't think Alan
better try it.
- [Tom] Might wanna take
the slack outta that rope.
- You stay behind.
- [Crow] You little pantywaist.
Boy if that was my kid,
I'd whack him.
- I'm okay, doc.
If you can make it, I can.
- Suit yourself.
- He's got it secure, let's go.
- [Joel] He's got tequila?
- [Tom] My blood pressure
is just racing.
- [Joel] Why don't they
just go around right there?
(shouting)
Don't fall, don't fall.
- [Crow] Jinx, jinx.
- [Tom] Noonan!
- [Joel] Noonan.
- [Crow] Jinx!
(screaming)
(all groan)
- [Crow] Hotfoot.
- [Tom] A gainer, yes it is.
- [Joel] Well I guess
he's not in the club.
- [Crow] Never did
like him anyway.
- You all right?
- Lousy.
That's what this
whole mission is.
- [Tom] Can I have his locker?
- What the hell are we
trying to prove, anyway?
Searching this stinkin'
nowhere planet
for a bunch of survivors
that may not exist?
- [Crow] Hey, I got
Angelo to think of!
- Take it easy, chief.
- Take it easy?
You watch a man die like that
and you say take it easy?
- [Joel] Hey, I thought
it was funny.
Why?
- You all right now, chief?
- Yes, sir.
- [Tom] Yeah, thanks for
not hitting me.
- Something just happened to me.
Got a little shook, I guess.
- Forget it, chief.
We're all a little shook.
- [Joel] Dickweed.
- We're almost there.
Let's move on.
- [Tom] Jerk.
- Come on, son.
- [Crow] I know how
you're feeling.
You see this shoulder?
It's here if you need it.
Idiot.
- [Joel] Now would you
go back across the log
and unhook the rope?
- [Tom] That makes me hungry.
- [Joel] Is it
primordial soup yet?
- [Crow] Now where did we park?
- [Joel] More of the same.
Oh brother.
- [Tom] Whose line is it?
- [Joel] Somebody.
(talking over each other)
- He's trying to
trick me isn't he?
Nobody could have
survived this crash.
- Bradley, you and the
chief wait here.
We can't be sure what
we might find inside.
You with me, doc?
- [Joel] Yeah, you two
disposable characters wait here.
- - [Crow] Wow, looks
like they turned that ship
into a restaurant.
I love these fern bars.
Looks like an
interstellar Denny's.
Great.
- [Joel] Wow, they had
more switches than we do.
(gasping)
- [Tom] Did you float an
air biscuit or is that me?
- Captain Ross?
- [Crow] Hey, their doggy
left all their bones here.
- [Joel] That's the people,
you dolt.
- [Crow] Oh.
- [Tom] Nice wallet.
- [Joel] That's his
sternum, don't touch it!
- I wanna check every
compartment in this ship.
I'm grabbing the chief here.
- [Joel] Huh, it says
"Thou shalt not ki--"
- [Crow] Uh, that was in
the other show.
- [Tom] It's a Close N' Play
- [Joel] It says,
"Ahab was obsessed
"with the Great White One."
It's a well, there's a
little girl down there!
- Well, it's the same situation
down in the maneuvering room.
The entire engineering crew.
- [Crow] The maneuvering room?
Don't you mean the bathroom?
- Just like it, too.
- There's one thing that
puzzles me, doc.
- [Crow] Fractions.
- One hatch is left
standing open.
And looks like some of
them have been forced.
- [Tom] Kinda like your
characterization.
- Someone else has
searched through the ship?
- Yeah, something like that.
- We've accounted for
all but five.
- There were five survivors.
- You mean that recorder
still works after 18 years?
- [Tom] Yep, it's on
eight-track.
- Emergency power pack,
it's as good as the day
it was installed.
Listen to this.
- [Recording] Now thete
are only three of us.
I don't expect
Sergeant Long to last
more than a few days now.
- [Crow] Long won't last long.
- [Recording] Has caused
lost of sight in both eyes,
and his brain seems to
have been damaged somehow.
I'm also certain that my
fever will soon overcome me.
There are no more drugs
aboard the ship.
- [Joel] This planet's
totally dry, dude.
Don't look to be scorin' nothin'
here.
- [Recording] Year one,
74th day.
- That's the last report.
- 74 long days.
Watching the sky,
waiting for us.
Waiting for death.
- [Crow] Nice speech, Jim.
- None of us knew it would
take us 18 years to get back.
The important thing is,
he knew we would.
- Thank god we did.
- You think they might be
alive, up in the mountains?
- It's possible.
(loud groaning)
- [Joel] Jim's constipated.
- Hey chief, what's wrong?
(screaming)
- What's wrong with him, doc?
- I don't know.
- [Joel] Why don't you ask him?
- Quick, get back!
- [Tom] Oh my god, how horrible,
to be killed by a plush toy!
- A tarantula.
Don't make amu quick moves.
Doc, keep perfectly still.
Let me have your laser gun.
- Yes, sir.
- [Crow] Kinda late now,
isn't it?
- Careful Scott, he sees you.
He can spring that far.
- [Tom] We rigged him that way.
- Look out, he's gonna jump!
(exploding)
- [Tom] The hopping
spider of Rylos !V.
- [Joel] Oh, I guess
he's really an angel now.
- I think he died more
from shock than the poison.
- Little lady seeks death.
- [Tom] Quick diagnosis.
- Let's go.
- [Crow] Well don't
everybody be so sad.
- What else is on the tape?
- [Joel] Eddie Money,
Two Tickets to Paradise,
that's about it.
The DeFranco Family.
I don't think you'd like it.
- Two of them did it.
They murdered Ross.
- This'll hit the
admiral pretty hard.
- Yeah.
Hit them pretty hard too, doc.
- [Tom] Wrecked 'em?
Damn near killed 'em!
- [Crow] And so Johnny Longtorso
and his industrial band of
bad boy spacefarin' pals
step out into the cold
air of Central Park.
(instrumental theme music)
- Oooh.
(Joel singing)
- I love it.
- [Tom] All that is is my
mother's shower curtain.
- Oh yes, Tang.
- [Joel] Crazy woman, I
offer her something to drink,
she thinks it's my name
all of a sudden.
- [Tom] What the?
- How long have your mother
and father been gone, Tang?
- [Crow] You mean frozen?
- [Tang] I was a child.
- Then who taught you
to speak, how to live?
- Mother teach.
She live until...
- [Tom] She held me
back in the third grade.
- Do you live here all alone?
- [Tang] Yes.
Alone.
- [Crow] If you don't
counf my 27 monkeys.
- Are there other people
on this planet?
- Yes, there are others.
Savages who hate and kill.
They do not want Tang to
live in their country.
- [Joel] Oh, you mean
Crash Orange,
Goofy Grape, Lefty Lemon,
that whole gang?
- Only enemies.
- But there is room for
many people to live here.
Why should they object?
- [Crow] Well, this is
the high rent district
and you know how people get.
- They are primitive men.
- [Tom] The producers?
- [Crow] No, these men
are different.
- [Tom] Oh, the
executive producers.
- [Crow] Natch.
- Who are different.
- [Joel] Oh wow, mom
never looked that good.
- Beautiful girl.
- My name is Linda.
- [Crow] My name is Lucky.
- Linda.
Tang.
- [Tom] I'm not just
for breakfast anymore.
- [Joel] Can I call
you Ovaltine?
- [Crow] I'll drink to that.
- Who undressed me?
(Tom clearing throat)
- Linda's clothes wet,
I undress.
- [Joel] Nice bag, Tang.
- I did not mean to hurt you.
- [Joel] I can love
only through pain.
- Do not be afraid of me.
- I am not afraid of you, Tang.
- [Tom] Dang-shang-alang, Tang.
- [Crow] Wang, bang,
thank you Tang.
(thunder rumbling)
♪ The weather started
getting rough ♪
- [Joel] The Tang and
she were tossed.
(thunder rumbling)
- [Crow] Dean will get
Liddy and the Plumbers
to do all the dirty work.
- [Recording] Navigation
officer, Cosmos Three.
- [Joel] Hey Crow, sounds
like one of the more
boring episodes of Prairie
Home Companion, huh?
- [Crow] Yeah, let's
get it on tape.
- That is the last.
That would place him in the
upper end of this canyon.
Probably a cave high
on the cliff.
There they'd be fairly safe--
- [Joel] Don't know
what you mean.
- Admiral, do you
seriously believe
any of them are still alive?
- [Joel] (mumbling) I don't
know what I think about it.
- Then why haven't they
used the radio?
Or continue to tape-record
beyond 74 days?
- He has a point, admiral.
- Even if we find nothing but--
(Joel mumbling)
- At least we'll be sure.
- Admiral King, qre the dead
worth more lives of the living?
- [Tom] What's a dead man
other than a live man
without any life?
- Sergeant Alan, the chief,
Linda.
- I'm not convinced that
Linda is dead either.
(Crow mumbling)
She might possibly be a captive.
- A captive?
- (mumbling) The serpent
was killed by a metal shaft,
possibly an arrow.
There might be primitive
man on this planet.
- [Tom] Men without
pocket squares.
- [Crow] Hey, did you
just get back
from the dentist or something?
- Tomorrow morning we're
gonna go out and find out.
(Tom mumbling)
- [Joel] Did he just
get a shot of Novocaine?
- [Crow] J.D.
(thunder rumbling)
- [Tom] Is it my breath?
[Joel] Oh, Captain
Crunch comfort ring,
help me out of this
awful jam now.
- [Crow] Shazam!
(cheerful music)
- [Joel] Yeah.
- [Crow] Go, Annette, go!
- [Joel] How'd she get the x-ray
machine to sound that good?
- [Tom] The space samba.
- [Crow] Wow, she'd be
perfect for your experiments.
- [Tom] A little girl
is trapped down there
and all you can do is dance!
It was murder.
- [Joel] Sexual harassment laws
are a lot looser in the future.
- You know you love it.
- Yeah, but not when we--
- [Crow] Six inches, come on.
- All right, break it up.
Mr. Bradley, didn't you
ever read the regulations
covering shipboard romances?
- Of course I did,
but this started
a long time before we
came aboard.
- [Crow] I can only
read Braille.
- 'Til you get back home,
or you'll find yourself
with a busted ensign.
- [Tom] A busted ensign,
we all know
how painful that can be.
- you wouldn't pull your
rank on a sweet little
junior officer like this,
just 'cause you're jealous.
- Mr. Bradley, there
are some men
who can send me
right into orbit.
You couldn't even get me
onto the launching pad.
- [Tom] Yikes, nice tag.
- Mr. Scott!
- [Crow] Oh, you're over
there, I didn't look.
Why isn't my field gear ready?
Bradley!
- Yes, sir!
- Where's Mr. Scott?
Why isn't the search party
ready to leave?
(Joel mumbling)
- He said you wouldn't
let anybody else go.
- Hmm.
He said that, did he?
- Those were your orders,
weren't they, admiral?
- Yes, yes it was.
(Joel mumbling)
Has he reported in yet?
- He said he would
investigate the waterfall area
and then report to you.
- Let me know the moment
you hear from him.
- [Tom] Thank you Betty,
Veronica, Jughead.
- Hey, you know something?
He didn't tell Scott to go.
He was gonna go himself.
- Yes, I know.
The commander told me
about it last night.
- [Joel] He was very high.
- [Crow] We've been walking
around this studio for months!
- [Tom] We've gone too far,
we're on the Indian set now,
turn back!
- Have you searched this
area thoroughly?
- She isn't here, admiral.
We can head for the cliff now,
I'll let you know if we
find anything.
Yes sir.
- [Joel] But your bath is ready,
sir.
- Doc, what kind of metal
would you say this is?
- Some kind of steel alloy?
- [Crow] Wrong, but
thanks for playing.
- What are you driving at?
- There's only one
kind of device
that shoots an arrow like this.
- [Tom] Uh, a bow.
- A crossbow.
Maybe a Centaurian crossbow.
- [Joel] Maybe.
- Doc, we might be on
the trail of
the very man who
murdered Captain Ross.
- [Joel] Let's go check out
the cave set, you slobs.
(cheerful music)
- [Joel] Hello, world!
- [Tom] Peter Pan and Wendy.
- [Crow] Hey, get me,
I'm a wood nymph!
- [Joel] My name isn't Tang,
it's Puck.
Oh, I meant to do my work today,
but the wildflowers beckoned,
and what could I do
but answer their calls?
Sweetly called by the
stringed lute, and I came.
- [Tom] That was beautiful.
- I remember this place, Tang.
It's so lovely here
and so peaceful.
- [Tom] This all flows from
the other huts upstream.
- Here I find Linda.
Come, we must speak.
- [Joel] I don't know if we
wanna watch this next part.
We'd better get outta here.
- [Crow] I kinda do.
- [Joel] No, you better stay,
come on.
(mechanical whirring)
(doors closing)
- No it's the green wire,
Joel, definitely the green.
- Look, who's holding the
screwdriver here anyway?
- I give up, who?
- Oh, that's enough
from the peanut gallery.
Thanks a lot, you two.
- Oh heck Joel, go ahead
and clip toe blue wire.
It's just a doomsday
machine, if it goes up
it's not like we're gonna be
around to experience oblivion.
- Well, by oblivion, do you mean
experiential oblivion or
phenomenological oblivion?
- Hmm, interesting distinction.
Let's define our terms,
shall we?
- Well, Kierkegaard
would always say--
- Listen you screwheads,
you'd better knock it off
or I'll brain you both
with my ball-peen hammer,
now knock it off.
- Hmm, interesting reaction
to a logically
defined supposition.
I think Camus would have
theorized differently.
- Oh listen, mister
smart-alec guy,
what wire would Camus cut?
- Uh, he'd cut the blue one
I think, and then if he was
still around after that,
he'd cut the green one.
- Eeenie, meenie, minie moe--
- Ah, the Samuel Beckett method.
- Joel, you're playing
dice with the universe.
I hope you realize that.
(bells chiming)
- [Satellite] Welcome,
you have passed through
the first three thresholds
of the Isaac Asimov
Literary Satellite,
Enter the disarm code or
enjoy the consequences.
Remember, this and all literary
works of the last century
are the sole property
of Isaac Asimov
and his many affiliates.
Thank you for intruding,
you have five seconds.
(bells chiming)
- Quick Joel, cut every wire!
- It's not gonna work,
it needs an access code!
- Uh, uh, try ego.
- Sideburns!
- I'll try I, Robot.
(buzzer buzzing)
- [Satellite] I'm sorry,
the correct entry
would have been copyright.
(groaning)
You now have six nanoseconds
to realize the consequences.
(all talking over each other)
- [All] Huh?
- This cockamamie satellite's
turned us all into
duplicate Isaac Asimovs!
- Hey, do you think
it's a conspiracy?
- Oh, no, I covered the
conspiracy topic
in my ten-volume history of
assassinations and coups.
- This is terrible, you guys!
- Oh, I don't know, at least now
I'll have something
to write about.
You know, I've been
thinking about
annotating the Manhattan
phone directory.
- Oh, look, it's
commercial sign.
That'll fit nicely
into my volume
on the effects of advertising
on the human psyche.
(all talking over each other)
(instrumental theme music)
- I've never seen such
beautiful fruit.
On Centaurus, at the
colony and on my ship,
we have only synthetic
fruit to eat.
- I know.
Mother speak of this
before she leave
on long journey beyond.
- [Tom] She's in the cave Tang,
frozen.
- This much better food.
- [Crow] They're Little
Debbie's cakes,
I gathered them from
the bear cave.
- [Tom] They're fit for a king.
Here King, here King!
Ba-boom, zing!
- You have much to learn.
- [Joel] Yeah, and
they're one-third
less calories than
regular mangoes.
- [Tom] You flunked third grade,
though.
(laughing)
- [Crow] Uh, turn it around.
No, the other way.
Oh, brother.
(Joel imitating monkey grunting)
- Kiko, my hungry friend.
- [Joel] Oh, he's still mad
about the whole evolution thing.
[Tom] Let me show you
how to open these things.
It's beautiful, look at this.
- [Joel] So I grow a pelt
and crawl up on a rock?
- Mmm!
This is even better
than the other.
- [Tom] The other what?
- [Crow] Can I have
another banana, Lancelot?
- Linda not hurt you,
she new friend.
- [Tom] Come on, show her
your red butt like at the zoo.
- Give Linda kiss.
(laughing)
Here, Kiko.
- [Crow] Nice babe you
got there, Tang.
- [Joel] Gotta go back to
my trainer now.
- [Crow] Now Tang's
really in love.
Oh, now he's gonna play some of
the world's most-loved
melodies, a la Zamfir.
(flute music)
- [Joel] Let me amuse and
cajole your species, Mata.
- [Tom] It's Peter and the wolf,
and the monkey, and
Ted and Alice.
(Kiko grunting)
Get me, I'm the master of
the pan flute.
- Linda like my friend Kiko?
- Yes, Tang.
- [Joel] And the monkey too?
- Linda like Tang's food?
- Yes.
- [Joel] Tang and Kiko,
they're cops.
- Linda like Tang?
- [Crow] Yeah, but I also like
other beverages like Hi-C.
Hey wait a minute, whose
legs are whose there?
- [Joel] Oh, I'm gonna
go spank myself.
- I will have to return
to my friends on the ship.
They will be worried for me.
- [Tom] I'm gonna have to
return to my cold shower.
- You like friends on ship
more than Tang.
- [Joel] Yeah, I guess I do.
Why?
(water rushing)
- What you say is not true,
Tang.
I love you.
Come on, help me with
the presents.
- No.
- [Crow] Tang's gonna
take a powder.
Wait, Tang is a powder.
(laughing)
- Linda, Tang can't swim.
- [Joel] Tang will settle
to bottom, must stir.
- Think Tang falling in
water very funny?
Maybe this funny too.
(screaming)
- [Tom] Russian judge
gives it a six.
- [Crow] Ah, she didn't come
out of her tuck in time.
(laughing)
(splashing)
- [Joel] See no evil.
Well, maybe just a little.
Yeah.
- [Crow] This week in The
Enquirer, Tang's recipe for
love.
Lots of good food, and
his water baby.
- [Tom] That's what I
can a complete breakfast.
Tang, Coke, milk and fruit.
[Joel] And booty.
- [Crow] Hey, get out of
the acid bath!
- [Tom] There's so much
to see, so much to do!
- Your ship.
- [Joel] Hey, I can see
your house from here.
- It's beautiful here.
- [Joel] And it's not even real.
- What is it, Tang?
- They will take Linda away.
- And Tang too.
We will go to a new
homeland together.
- No, mother and
father are here.
This is my homeland.
This is Linda's home.
- Yes, Tang.
- [Crow] Tang's never
heard of a one-night stand.
- But I have to tell
the admiral.
- Why tell admiral?
- He's my friend!
He's like a father.
(Tom clearing throat)
The only one I've ever known.
- [Tom] Ah, Lolita...
- Like your father.
We will go to him.
- [Joel] The frozen dad?
- [Tom] It's the Monkees,
get out of there!
Scamper, cheese it!
- [Joel] They're too busy
spearin' to put anybody down.
- Linda, across!
- Tang, Tang!
- [Tom] Tang kwan do.
- [Crow] Those, ladies
and gentlemen,
are the planet's
fiercest warriors.
(screaming)
- [Joel] Hey everybody,
I'm Bruce Lee!
(screaming)
- [Crow] Looks like the
family from It's About Time.
- [Crow] Yeah, you're
lucky my chick's here, man.
- [Joel] He's fighting a bunch
of Sonny Bono lookalikes.
(gun firing)
(screaming)
(exploding)
- Help, help!
- Linda!
Linda!
- [Crow] Ah, typical response.
I don't understand it,
so I better shoot it.
(screaming)
- Tang!
Let me go!
Let me go, let me go!
- [Crow] Hey, he's giving
her a shot with a corkscrew.
- [Joel] Darn jocks,
always taking my girl.
I'm gonna leave this
darn chess club.
- Why was she trying to go back,
doc?
(instrumental theme music)
- I'm sure that Scott
would have found him by now
if the wound was
really critical.
(mumbling)
- Look, take it from me, David.
If that boy can be
found, Scott'll find him.
- Bradley just reported in.
They've lost the trail.
It stopped suddenly at
the edge of a cliff.
- [Crow] There was a note.
It said, "Aaaaah!"
- [Joel] Hey, what do
you think that means?
- The volcano's going to erupt.
This planet won't be safe.
Radio Mr. Scott to
return to the ship.
- [Tom] Is it my breath?
- [Crow] It is his breath.
(yelling)
- [All] What?
- Try once more, Jung.
(yelling)
- [Joel] Try something
that means something.
- I believe it's hopeless,
commander.
- Admiral King wants us to
report back to the ship.
He's afraid Old Smokey over
there's gonna blow its top
and shake the walls down
to the canyon.
- [Tom] No, you're thinking
of the Big Bad Wolf.
- Let's go.
- [Crow] Okay, I'll
just stay here
and then I'll be here
if you need me.
- [Joel] Bye, Chang.
- [Crow] Hey, it's
Cliff Robertson.
Hi, I'm a mountain.
(chuckles)
Stupid.
(earthquake rumbling)
- [Joel] What are the chances
of those idols falling over?
- [Crow] Billy Idol?
- [Tom] Uh oh, stock footage
and lots of it, coming at us.
- Sorry, sir.
- [Crow] Hey, what were you
doing in the washing machine?
- [Tom] How are those chicks
coming along, hatched yet?
- Mr. Scott, prepare
the ship for departure.
- Yes, sir.
- I hate you!
I hate all of you!
- [Joel] Gee, don't say hi.
- Sergeant Evans.
Crew to stations.
- Yes, sir.
Attention, all personnel.
Outland stations,
outland stations.
- Raise the ramp.
- [Crow] Raise the rent?
Hey, I've got a lease, pal!
- Linda!
- [Joel] Linda!
(rumbling)
- [Joel] More stock footage.
- [Tom] Hit the deck!
- [Crow] What is that?
- Linda!
Linda!
(rumbling)
- [Crow] Thwow them to the
gwound, pwanet, most woughlu.
Thank you.
(rumbling)
- [Joel] Oh, I hit my butt,
it's all hot and it hurts
and stuff, ow.
Uh, let me slow it down
one more time.
Guys, I got a feeling it's
call-back time.
There's a girl down that well!
- [Tom] But the chicks are done.
[Crow] Anyone in the
washing machine?
- [Joel] Where's Fang, anyway?
(rumbling)
This is no time for push-ups,
you dolt.
- Get the ship out of here, Mr.
Scott.
- [Crow] Good thing I've got
my Farah action slacks on.
- [Tom] Linda!
Linda!
(rumbling)
- [Crow] Magma.
Hey, I can't finish my
jumble puzzle.
- Quick!
You get back to the ship,
that's an order!
- We're north going back!
- I can't leave her here.
- [Tom] Then let go of me!
- Leave me here.
I have to find her!
Don't you understand?
She's my responsibility!
She's all I have,
Linda's my daughter.
- [All] Uh-oh...
- [Crow] Geez, talk about
deus ex machina.
(rumbling)
- [Tom] Yellowstone.
Boy, they're really rockin'
this place.
- [Crow] This is what happens
after you eat at Lollapalooza.
Looks like the land
of Dairy Queen.
- [Joel] Fire up the wok,
dinner's ruined again.
- [Crow] Hey, look out,
the styrofoam is on fire!
(eerie humming)
- Tang?
- [Tom] This is great, I
feel like E.T.
- Tang?
- [Joel] I'm back!
Hi, girl.
(Tom yelling like Tarzan)
- [Crow] Remember when
we were dating
and we met right here
at this pool of filth?
- [Joel] This is great, she
can meet his frozen parents.
- Tang!
Oh, Tang.
- Linda!
- [Tom] Let's make some
static with these pelts.
You still haven't
scrubbed your pits.
That's okay, I love you,
you big breakfast drink.
- [Crow] Come on, I've
really changed the place.
The monkey moved in, I hope
that doesn't bother you.
- [Joel] Why is this called
Planet of the Prehistoric Women,
it makes no sense.
- Stand by, vertical
gravitators.
- [Crow] Boy, they really got
a lot done on that planet.
- [Computer] Vertical
gravitators.
- Hold it, Scott!
- They're alive, admiral.
Linda and the boy, look!
Attention, attention.
- [Joel] Oh, hi Elvis.
- [Crow] I'd like to sing
some of my hits,
and then I'm going down
to the galley
to have some peanut
butter and 'nana sandwich.
- [Tom] You too, Elvis.
- Well, Mr. Scott, let's
get about going home.
- You mean we're not going
back for them, admiral?
- No, I will not go back.
- [Joel] Not today.
- They'll be happy here.
They belong here, they
belong to each other.
- [Crow] Who are you,
Chuck Woolery?
- They'll create a
world of their own.
- [Joel] I'm feeling
loud, proud and brassy.
- People from their homeland.
- [Crow] Except for
the master race.
- [Tom] I'm sure you're
right, you rotless bastard.
- Activate control.
- Yes, sir.
The admiral's a different man.
- [Joel] I know our affair
wasn't set up in this film,
but let's be part of the
loose ends festival anyhow.
(Tom grunting)
- [Joel] Hey look, you
can see my house.
- [Crow] Drive me to the mall.
- [Tom] We got a planet
to populate, honey.
- [Joel] I'm already bored,
Tang.
- Make an entry in
the ship's log.
(Tom mumbling)
- To the third planet
of the Solaris system.
As this planet was
heretofore unknown,
(Joel mumbling)
from this day forward, the
third planet of Solaris
will be known as the
blue planet.
We designate it planet Earth.
- [Joel] Earth?
- [Crow] Oh come on,
who made you God?
- [Tom] Oh, man evolved
from Tang, right.
We'd better get outta
here, we'd better go.
- [Joel] My great-grandmother
was really, really hot!
- [Crow] Was she?
- [Joel] We gotta go figure
out a way to clean this...
(mechanical whirring)
(doors closing)
Hey, you know what?
These Isaac Asimov
sideburns come off.
- They're just taped on!
- They're phony.
- Oh, that's what it means
to be Isaac Asimov, I guess.
- Yeah, but he probably
already thought of that.
- Yeah.
Instead of a doomsday machine,
I guess it kinda turned out
to be a dorksday machine.
- It could be worse.
- Oh?
- It could have been a
Doris Day machine.
(groaning)
(laughing)
- Come on you guys, it's time
to read some letters here.
Okay, Cambot, let's...
Oops, you lost your head.
- (laughing) Oh, my skull.
- Oh that's too bad,
that's okay.
Here we go.
- All right.
- Put this up on the screen.
MST 3000, I am writing
a response to you guys.
In one of your episodes
in specific, I believe
Robo Holocaust was the
name, the one in which
a man possesses valuable
knowledge and was transformed
into a vegetable-like
being because of his
inability to cooperate--
- Avocado boy!
- Yep.
And we had a contest to
see who could come up with
a name for the avocado
guy, and here's his entry.
He's the winner, by the way.
Here, he gave us four.
Skip, the couch potato.
Let's have a picture of
that guy, Cambot.
A Man from P.R.O.D.U.C.E,
A Weeble-O named Chloro-Phil,
and the Eight Wonder of
the Guacamole, so.
(laughing)
That's from James S.
Callstrom, from Bloomington.
- The winner of the brainstorm.
- Yeah, he won the brainstorm.
Thanks to all who entered
that one, by the way.
And here's this next one.
Dear Sir or Bot, one lonely,
depressing Saturday night,
I happened to switch to
channel 49, and found MST 3000.
It was love at first laugh,
I was instantly hooked.
Now my life has meaning.
- That's pretty sad, really.
- Anyway, it's a great show.
I've shown it to
several of my friends
and they say they all like it.
Even my wife likes it
and she is not an SF fan.
What's SF mean?
- Uh, San Francisco.
- Oh, okay.
Anyway, the last one here is
from a father and daughter.
- [Tom] Do they dance too?
- [Joel] I don't know.
We would like information
about the fan club.
We would also like to
know if there's
a special club group
for Tom Servo.
- You betcha!
- Wow.
Ever since his head
exploded trying to think of
something good to say
about The Bride Vanishes,
we realized he has a
rare and special honesty.
It's good that you didn't
ask for good comments about
Project Moonbase, the
consequences would be
unthinkable.
That's from Kenneth--
- I shudder at the thought.
- Yeah.
Kenneth J. Plotkin and Sarah
E. Plotkin, the Plotkin family.
Well, that's it.
Tom Servo, you wanna give
'em the mailing address?
- Sure!
- Cambot, put it up on
the screen there.
- Love to, it's the Mystery
Science Theater 3000
Information Club, P.O. Box 5325,
Hopkins, Minnesota, 55343.
- All right, that's the
end of the experiment.
What do you think, sirs?
♪ I think I'll file this
thing for you ♪
♪ As I always seem to do ♪
♪ I like working for you, Clay ♪
♪ 'Cause you're a
really neat guy ♪
- Well, I think you
should file this, Larry.
Until next time, pasty boy.
(Slow solemn theme music)